Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Tsimpouki, Dora, undated (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Tufts University, undated (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Tulsa Library System, undated (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Turner Free Library, undated (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Turtle Bay Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - TV Guide, undated (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - The Mark Twain House, undated (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Twomey, Tom, undated (Box 20, Folder 112)
  - "U", undated (Box 20, Folder 113)
  - UJA-Federation Campaign, undated (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - U.K. Year of Literature and Writing, undated (Box 20, Folder 115)
  - Ulster, University of-, undated (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Ungerer, Miriam, undated (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Union League Club, undated (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - United Nations, undated (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Unity House, undated (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Up Here Magazine, undated (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Updike, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - U.S. Copyright Office, undated (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - U.S. Department of Justice, undated (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - U.S. Department of State, undated (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - U.S. District Court-Eastern District of Pennsylvania, undated (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - U.S. Information Agency, undated (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - U.S. News & World Report, undated (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - U.S. Postal Service, undated (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - USA Today, undated (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Utah, University of-, undated (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - "V", undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Vagabond, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Valentine, Jean, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Van Egdom, Lea, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Van Toorn, W. P., undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Vanden Heuvel, Katrina, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Versluys, Kristiaan, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Very Special Arts, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Vestoff, Virginia, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Administration, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Viener, Saul, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Viking Press, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Village Reform Democratic Club, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Villanova University, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Vintage Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Tech University, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Virginia, University of-, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Visiting Artist Series, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Vitale, Alberto, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Vogel, Viveka, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Vogue Magazine, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Volvox Globator, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - von der Lippe, Angela, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "Wa-Wh", undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - "Wi-Wz", undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Wachsman, Edith and Rita, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Wachtel, Chuck, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Wagner, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Wakin, Eleanor, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Walden Woods Project, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Walker, C. Jr., undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Harry Walker, Inc., undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Wall Street Journal, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Wallace, Joan, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Walnut Street Theatre, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Walt Disney Studios, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Walton, David, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Walton, Tony, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Wang, Chull, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - War Resisters League & Mobilization for Survival, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Warner Books, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Warner / Chappell Music, Inc., undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - The Washington Post, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - The Washington School, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - The Washington Spectator, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Washington State University, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Washington University, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Water Mill Museum, undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Watkins, Ed, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Waxenberg, Barbara, undated (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Wayne State University, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - The Way Out Magazine, undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - WBAI, undated (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - WCNY-TV, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - WDR, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - [re:] Webber, Andrew Lloyd, undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Webber Studies, undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - WEHM, undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Weinstein, Wendy, undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Weisburg, Larry, undated (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Weisburg, Richard, undated (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Weiss, Philip, undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Weissler, Barry, undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Weissman, Sy, undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Weller, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Wellesley College, undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Wells, Dean Faulkner, undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Welty, Eudora, undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Wernblad, Annette, undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Werner, Nat, undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Wesley College, undated (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - West Hartford Public Library, undated (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - West, William, undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Westchester Arts Council, undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Westchester Coalition for Legal Abortion, undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Westchester Community College, undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Westchester County Clerk, undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Westchester Library Association, undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Westchester Reform Temple, undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Westchester Rockland Newspapers, undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - WestEd, undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Western Illinois University, undated (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Westigen Review of Poetry, undated (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - WETA, undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Weybright, Victor, undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Wheatland Foundation, undated (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Wheeler, Susan / Philip Furmanski, undated (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - White, Frank and Virginia, undated (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - The White House, undated (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - White, J. P., undated (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - White, Marion, undated (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - White Plains Public Library, undated (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Whitman, Alden, undated (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Walt Whitman Birthplace Association, undated (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, undated (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Who's Who in America, undated (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - WHYY, undated (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - WICE, undated (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - Wiener, Jon, undated (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Wigwag, undated (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - Wilbur Multimedia, undated (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Wildcliff Natural Science Center, undated (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Wilding, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - Wilensky, Thomas, undated (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Wiley, W. Bradford, undated (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Wilhelm, Douglas, undated (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - William and Mary, College of-, undated (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - William Patterson College, undated (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Williams College, undated (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Williams, Galen, undated (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Williams, Oscar, undated (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Williamstown Theatre Festival, undated (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Willrich, Patricia Rowe, undated (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - H. W. Wilson Company, undated (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - The Woodrow Wilson Center, undated (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - Windows on the Writing Life, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Winfield House, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Winter, Warner, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Brian Winthrop International, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Winthrop, Elizabeth, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Wisconsin, Madison, University of-, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin, Milwaukee, University of-, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Wisconsin, Stevens Point, University of-, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - University of Wisconsin Press, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - [re:] Wiseman, Thomas, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Witness, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Witten, Suzy, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - WLIW 21, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - WNYC, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Wolcott, Alison, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Wolfe, Burton, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Wolfe, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Wolfe Society, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Wolff, Renate (Mrs. Philip Goepp), undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Wolff, Tobias, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Woman's Club of New Rochelle, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Women's Campaign Fund, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Women's Project & Productions, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - T. W. Wood Art Gallery / Vermont College, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Woodman, George, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Woods, Eugene, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - WOR, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Worker Writing, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Workman Publishing, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - The World After Nuclear War, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - World Link, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - World Literature Today, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Worldnet, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Worrall, Simon, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Wright, Elizabeth, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Wright, James and Annie, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Writer Nights, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Writers and Artists for Peace in the Middle East, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Writers & Books, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Writers & Publishers Alliance, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Writers' and Publishers' Alliance for Nuclear Disarmament, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - The Writer's Center, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - The Writers Community, undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Writer's Digest, undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Writers Guild of America, East, Inc., undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - The Writer's Voice, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - The Writer's Workshop, undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - The Writing Self Quarterly, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Wutz, Michael, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - "Y", undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Yablonsky, Linda, undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - The Yacht, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Yaddo, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre, undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Yale University, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Yang, Renjing, undated (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Yankee Doodle Society, undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Yardley, Ilsa, undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Yeh, Carol, undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Yeshiva University, undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Yleisradio RTV, undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Y.M. & Y.W.H.A., undated (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Yonkers Public Library, undated (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Young Children Priority One, undated (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - "Z", undated (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Zarzecki, Krzysztof, undated (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Zen Community of New York, undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Zimm, Howard, undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Zimmer, Dieter, undated (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Zmora, Bitan, Modan Publishers, undated (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Zeotrope, undated (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Zohar, Rita, undated (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Zoland Books, undated (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Zuckerman, Eugenia, undated (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Miscellaneous / Unidentified from Doctorow, undated (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Rosenblatt, Roger (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Mailer memorial (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Sag Harbor (Box 77, Folder 4-6)
  - Wilbur letters, child's drawing, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - New York Times articles, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Promotional material (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Goldsmith galley, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Financial documents (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Novels
    - Welcome to Hard Times (short story titled "The Bad Man From Brodie"), undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (work-in-progress drafts)-Part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (work-in-progress drafts)-Part 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (work-in-progress drafts)-Part 3, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (early drafts with corrections and notes), undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (outline and notes), undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (first 46 pages and outline for chapter 4 through the conclusion), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (various drafts, some with corrections), undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (typescript draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (typescript draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (typescript draft), undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (carbon-copy draft with corrections), undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (galleys), undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Welcome to Hard Times (paperback edition galleys), undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Big as Life (original, unrevised draft with discarded pages and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Big as Life (original, unrevised draft with discarded pages and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Big as Life (original, unrevised draft with discarded pages and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Big as Life (original, unrevised draft with discarded pages and notes)-Part 4, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Big as Life (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Big as Life (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Big as Life (early draft with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Big as Life (original, revised draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Big as Life (original, revised draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Big as Life (original, revised draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 3, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Big as Life (draft titled, The Benediction)-Part 3, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Big as Life (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Big as Life (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Big as Life (unidentified draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Big as Life (notes and fragments), undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Big as Life (xerox copy draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Big as Life (xerox copy draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Big as Life (xerox copy draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Big as Life (xerox copy draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Big as Life (xerox copy draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Big as Life (final draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Big as Life (final draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Big as Life (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Big as Life (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Book of Daniel (original draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Book of Daniel (original draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - The Book of Daniel (notebook), undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - The Book of Daniel (early fragments with corrections and notes), undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - The Book of Daniel (early fragments with corrections and notes), undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - The Book of Daniel (early draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - The Book of Daniel (early draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - The Book of Daniel (unidentified drafts with corrections), undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The Book of Daniel (unidentified draft with corrections and notes), undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - The Book of Daniel (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - The Book of Daniel (draft titled, Save the Isaacsons), undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - The Book of Daniel (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - The Book of Daniel (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Book of Daniel (incomplete draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - The Book of Daniel (incomplete draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - The Book of Daniel (revised draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - The Book of Daniel (revised draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - The Book of Daniel (xerox copy draft), undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - The Book of Daniel (xerox copy draft), undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The Book of Daniel (xerox copy draft), undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Book of Daniel (xerox copy draft), undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - The Book of Daniel (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - The Book of Daniel (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - The Book of Daniel (design copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - The Book of Daniel (design copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - The Book of Daniel (galleys), undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - The Book of Daniel (galleys), undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - The Book of Daniel (master set-1/26/1971), undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - The Book of Daniel (uncorrected proof), undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (hand-written draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (first draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (first draft revised)-Part 1, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (first draft revised)-Part 2, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (incomplete second draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (second revised draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (unidentified draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (draft with corrections, 8/9/1982) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (copy of draft with corrections, 8/9/1982) (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (draft with comments and correspondence from Haskell Wexler), undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (unidentified draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (unidentified draft), undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Daniel: a screenplay by E.L. Doctorow (edited by Paul Levine, annotated), undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (Copy C, final draft, 8/9/1982) (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (draft, 8/9/1982) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - The Book of Daniel-screenplay (Copy B, final draft with transposed visit scene, 8/9/1982) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - The Book of Daniel-movie version (screen cues and production handbook), undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - The Book of Daniel-movie version (movie stills), undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - The Book of Daniel-movie version (music), undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Ragtime (original draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime (original draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime (notes), undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime (revised draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime (revised draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 1, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 2, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections and notes)-Part 3, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime (revised sections with corrections), undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime (incomplete draft with corrections), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Ragtime (incomplete copy of draft with corrections), undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime (xerox copy of pages 84-119), undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited draft, 3/4/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited draft, 3/4/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime (galleys, 3/6/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Ragtime (galleys, 3/6/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited galleys, 4/9/1975)-Part 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Ragtime (copy-edited galleys, 4/9/1975)-Part 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (original draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (original draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (early drafts with corrections)-Part 3, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unedited draft)-Part 3, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 1, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft)-Part 2, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (draft by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (second draft, first revision by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections by Michael Weller and E.L. Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (unidentified draft with corrections by Michael Weller and E.L.Doctorow), undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Ragtime-screenplay (copy), undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime-musical script (first draft), undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Ragtime-musical script (early draft with correspondence, 4/11/1994) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Ragtime-musical script (marked "GHD Ragtime notes" 2/10/1995) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 8/26/1995) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 2/16/1996) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 5/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 7/26/1996) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/3/1996) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Ragtime-musical script (draft, 9/17/1996) (Box 30, Folder 10)